I never dreamed before
I'm gonna knock the door
into the world of perfect free
(You ain't no lonely!)
You're gonna say I'm lying
I'm gonna get the chance
I thought a chance is far from me
(You ain't no lonely!)
I was made to hit in America
(I was made to hit in America)
You are the sun, you are the star
(To me, forever)
I was made to hit in America
(I was made to hit in America)
You're seriously thinking
about the revival of BECK,
so I wondered if I could help.
And what did Chiba-kun say?
You will be dead!
The conversation ended
in the worst way possible.
It's so like Chiba-kun.
-This is nothing to laugh at!
-Mmm.
-Still...That ramen is bad!
-That ramen is bad!
"Condor Ramen"
Hello!
-Hey...
-Chiba-kun, I...
Were you the one who sent Maho?
Huh...Err, no...
Hah! Spouting her mouth off!
What did Maho say?
That there's no future
in bad-tasting ramen...
so I should join up
with BECK when they regroup.
That's all she kept saying.
Chiba-kun!
Huh?
Let's revive BECK...one more time.
Well...I'm the only one right now...
Sorry, but right now...
I can only think about ramen.
Hey, Koyuki!
Is my ramen...that bad?
Yeah...
Are you serious about BECK?
I have to be serious...
or there won't be another BECK!
I can come back?
I don't have to have a dream?
What're you saying, Chiba-kun?!
You're so late!
I've been regretting it since
the day after Grateful Sound...
Why'd that...
Chiba-kun!
But I can't make it up with Ryusuke!
Chiba-kun...
Taira-kun is awesome!
That band was something else!
Hurry it up before Taira leaves!
Yeah...But if we're too hasty...
Taira-kun!
Hey, nice to see you.
Taira...Yoshiaki's calling for you.
Be right there.
-Actually, I wanted to ask you
to return to BECK once...
-I got it.
-Huh?
-You're regrouping BECK?
Yes.
I was planning to agree only
if you came to see me.
-Taira-kun...
-Hey, hey...
-Taira-kun!
-Idiot!
I'm a member of Heroes now,
so I can't commit immediately.
After the promotional tour,
I'll work it out with them.
Taira-kun...
However...I'm agreeing to return...
...on the condition that all
five original members come back.
Huh?!
Otherwise, I want nothing
to do with this.
Taira-kun...
Sorry, but I'm busy. See ya.
Well then, the big problem
here is Ryusuke.
Yeah...
Maybe...he's no longer in Japan.
Even if he's away,
I think our spirit is one.
"Saito Paper Company"
Koyuki-kun, can you throw this out?
Sure.
Koyuki-kun, can you go shopping?
I have a date with Momo-chan.
All right.
"Chinese Restaurant Sing Lung"
I'm back.
Oh, welcome home...
Was there a phone call for me?
No, there wasn't.
I see.
Man, that was a fantastic
live performance!
If you told me you were coming,
I'd have put you down as guests.
Taira-san, will you
take a picture with me?
Sure.
This is from Koyuki.
Hey, Chiba!
Don't keep your fan waiting,
you sexy rocker!
Idiot!
That Koyuki...
There's a strange rumor
spreading among the fans.
Yeah...Something about you
leaving Heroes after the tour.
To rejoin BECK.
I mean, geez...
Why would anyone quit Heroes,
which is gonna sell 200,000 CDs?
Hey, Taira!
Wanna listen?
-Huh?
It's a rough cut.
But the genius shines through.
I'm amazed he wrote so many songs.
Huh?
For everything up to now,
thank you so much!
Think of me as a fool.
But I'm going to return to BECK.
-Are you kidding?!
-No shit?!
Hey, Ryusuke Minami!
Ho man, what a surprise!
How long you been here
in New York?
Mr. Davis...
Okay, Ryusuke Minami...
If I can help, I'll give you a hand.
I really appreciate it, Mr. Davis.
Doitashimashite. [You're welcome]
Yukio! Phone call!
Okay!
Hello?
Huh?! Yeah.
Sorry to keep you waiting, Koyuki.
-Saku!
-It took me a while
to save enough money.
You're late!
-Sorry.
-I was so worried!
Koyuki...
You haven't been
in touch lately, either.
I wanted to come earlier...
Saku...
Koyuki...
...just have to Stage Dive or Die
Mind blower, a shower of sweat
Run towards a new world, my life
Those who seek it will be rewarded
Pass the hot shot
Keep on coming, come on!
Blow your mind
Squeeze your sweat yeah
Your old man is stubborn.
I couldn't convince him,
had'ta run away.
Had'ta?
You can stay at my house for as long
as it takes to find an apartment.
I'm sa'happy.
Sa'happy?
Uh! Typhoon! Typhoon 24!
24-7! Non-stop...
Yukio, there's a phone call
from someone named Sato.
All right!
Hello?
Congratulations on the revival of BECK!
O-Oh, thank you.
I'll get right to the point.
Yes?
There's an offer for BECK
for an American tour.
America?
Hello?
Hey, what's up?
I heard about you from John.
I want to make a deal with you.
I have a most valuable tape here
which I got from Eddy Lee.
I'll give you this,
instead I want you to leave
Mongolian Chop Squad alone forever.
Right. Some deal...
I'll bring the tape to
your hotel tonight anyway.
You sure are a crazy dumb ass.
If you never change
I think there is no way my life fizzle out
You open up the door with negative aura
(I'm fed up fed up fed up)
You say future is murky indeed...
I'm sick of hearing gripe.
An American tour?!
That's unbelievable!
Does that mean we
can throw television sets
out the window like
Lead Zeppelin and the Stones...
and fly around in groovy jets and stuff?
Idiot! It's a hard tour...driving across
ten cities to perform in rock venues.
-Ohh...
-Still, it's unbelievable.
A band member of
a group called F.V.E.
Saw us at Grateful Sound
and made the offer.
-We've gotta do it!
-Think carefully!
Huh?!
Without Ryusuke...it's too risky
for BECK to do an American tour.
But...
It's not like us to turn down
a chance like this!
But it's dangerous.
America, huh...
-We'd better get passports.
-Does that cost money?
Summer vacation ended with BECK
rehearsals day in and day out.
Man, look how dark you got!
And you're so white!
-Shaddup!
-Koyuki-kun, Saku-chan told me...
But are you really
dropping out of school?
Yeah.
Koyuki-kun...
I was hoping to
just fade out slowly...
But with the American tour coming up,
I figured it's good timing.
Aww...It'll be lonely without you guys.
Sorry.
America, huh?
It's too far, I can't go.
Farewell!
This is an announcement
from the Student Council.
On the 26th from 3pm...
...my sister.
We began exhausting live performances
to prepare for the American Tour.
In this world, which everyone is lonely.
We began exhausting live performances
to prepare for the American Tour.
In this world, which everyone is lonely.
Yeah.
If you are at a loss as to what to do.
Raise you stiff middle finger.
It will know which way the wind blows.
Our last performance was at the Marquee.
Our next live performance in town...
None!
Because BECK is starting a grueling 50-day,
46-city tour of the United States!
-BECK is the best!
-Chiba!
Uh! Typhoon! Typhoon 24!
24-7! Non-stop...
For this last live performance,
Chiba dove into the audience for the close.
Man, that was painful! Yes.
Huh? How was BECK?
Your guitar was great.
Really?
Yeah.
See ya.
Koyuki, wasn't that...
Hyodo. He was here as a guest.
Is he in a band?
They disbanded recently
and he's looking for new members.
Oh...
He said good luck
on our American Tour.
Oh yeah?
Don't kid yourself!
I guess taking off for two months is...
Damn right!
Then I'll have to quit.
It's easy to replace
someone like you!
Thank you for everything.
America, huh?
Don't lose to the guys over there!
Yes!
Slip out of...
Slip out ob.
Out of!
Out ob.
You're hopeless!
You leave tomorrow!
If you can't pronounce
something like this,
you'd better not go to America!
Well Maho, you have
a hard time writing kanji.
We're not talking about me!
Can't you be a little more gentle?
Well, excuse me
for not being gentle.
You're so petty!
You can drop dead
in America, Koyuki!
Stupid Maho!
This is Tanaka...I had reservations
for 2 at 7 o'clock.
I'm sorry, but I have to cancel.
Sorry.
-Koyuki-kun, Maho forgot this.
-Huh?
This is...
"Lesson Cassette: 'Slip Out', For Koyuki"
Maho...
What a fool
I don't know 'bout tomorrow
What it's like to be
Yukio, do you have your passport?
Yup.
Then say goodbye to your father.
All right.
Did you call Grandma?
Yup.
No matter how many times
I look at it, it's a rough schedule.
Are we really gonna
make it in 50 days?
What will be will be!
That's all there is to know!
Umm...Is this it?
Hey, it's so blurred!
All right, there's the American continent!
-Is that the wing of the jet?
-Uh-huh.
David Eric of the popular
F.V.E. Band came to pick us up.
He's out of focus.
-This is an alien base.
-No, it's the L.A. Airport.
-Our hotel.
-Hey, pretty nice!
This was the only nice hotel.
-Umm...Chiba-kun studying.
-Some study.
-We performed live here.
-It says Mongolian Chop Squad!
But we just couldn't get it together.
-The audience is looking down.
-Chiba is depressed.
Put it on spin!
-These are members of other bands.
-Where are you, Koyuki?
-We traveled in this car.
-Saku's practically kissing the windshield!
-Hey, lots of people!
-We're not performing.
-Look at the color of her hair!
-The Lizards. That's a guy.
Huh!?
We sold our CDs.
We sold quite a bit actually.
Hmm...
-This is the car we traveled in.
-Looks so American.
-We're frogs.
-Silly!
-This is the car...
-I get it already!
Hey, are they clowns?
-This live was great.
-But I can't see you.
It was great! Hurrah for Long Beach!
-We had a session together.
-What're you doing, Koyuki?
-Oh, you had a flat tire.
-Yes.
That's Chiba-kun.
-Look at the clouds!
-It's more awesome when
you actually see them.
Hmm...
-Oh, another session?
-Taira-kun was popular even in America.
-And here's Chiba-kun.
-Koyuki, you look so cute.
We were near total exhaustion.
-Looks like fun.
-A short moment of relaxation.
-Here we are in New York!
-This picture's so dark!
-Taking a stroll in New York.
-Did you eat hot dogs?
Yup!
This is CBGB.
The audience is to the right.
-And this is...
-That's the man...New York Punk.
Who is he?
He's Kevin Eric. The guitarist
and leader of F.V.E.
-He's David's older brother.
-Hmm...
-It's blurred again!
-Well, Kevin's a scary guy.
-And this guy...
-Yup, that's...
Umm...Texas, I think.
-We even traveled
through a place like this.
-Hmm...
-Golden Gate Bridge.
-That's San Francisco!
-And this is...
-Seattle.
And that's Pike Place Market.
-A supermarket?
-You can see fish jumping.
And the Space Needle.
And Jimi Hendrix.
Chiba-kun had a dream.
And he heard Jimi say,
"Let's meet at my grave."
-Grave?
-And the day was September 18.
-The day mentioned in Ryusuke's message.
-And also, the day Jimi Hendrix died.
Koyuki, you're cut off.
-This is Jimi Hendrix's grave.
-Hmm...
And...we found Ryusuke.
Beck and Keith, too?
Yep.
It's blurred again.
Oh, this is the newspaper article.
-So Leon was arrested.
-And Ryusuke was right there.
I'm so glad he's alive!
-Oh, you saw this already.
-Yeah.
And...we met up with Ryusuke,
who had Lucille,
at the Crocodile Cafe in Seattle.
It was the first time all five members
were together since coming to America.
Now this is BECK!
-Koyuki, let's do "Slip Out."
-Right.
I don't know since when I changed
to such a cold-hearted guy.
I have to warm this frozen icy
lonely heart to thaw.
I like being wrapped with warmness
more than anything else for sure.
I'm gonna make my coming days
to be filled with laughter and joy
Hey, what're you doing?!
I let myself down that I'm more cruel
then I thought I would be.
Stop teasing him!
I let myself down that I'm more cruel
then I thought I would be.
Shut up! Let's go, everyone!
Beck! Come here!
I told you,
you shouldn't go out alone.
You...
You made me worry.
A foreigner?
Isn't this dog ugly?
Thank you for saving Beck.
Sorrow isn't what I am,
but its growing my sensation
Regrets taught me how
to make any hard decisions.
Peace is always by my side
but I've never felt it once.
Love is not the word only
for the sweet romance. Yeah.
Well I'm scared, I'm scared,
I'm scared, I'm scared to death.
And I'm scared to keep on
going on my way. Yeah.
Well I'm scared, I'm scared,
I'm scared, I'm scared to death.
And I tell myself
I'm special till the end.
I don't give my heart to no one
cause I don't wanna waste my time.
I tried to love this loneliness
to slip out of lonesome hole.